

### **Matheus Vaillant**

# Full-stack Web Developer

#### Hello!

I'm Matheus Vaillant, a web developer based in Peniche, Portugal.
I enjoy creating things that live on the internet, whether that be websites, applications, or anything in between. My goal is to always build products that provide pixel-perfect, performant experiences.

### Get in touch!

# **GitHub:** mathvaillant

#### Mobile:

+351 920 508 532

#### Email:

matheusvaillant505@gmail.com

#### Website:

matheusvaillant.com

### LinkedIn:

mattvaillant

### Skills

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Sass
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- Bootstrap
- MaterialUI
- Git/Github
- Firebase
- APIs, JSON
- NodeJs
- Figma Design
- Materiallize, Tailwind
- Express
- Google Cloud Services
- MongoDB
- Agile Methodologies

## Work Experience

### Software Engineer at Planless.io 06/2021 - present

Currently working as a full-stack software engineer using mainly JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJs, Redux, MongoDB, and Google Cloud Services. With a broad range of work both on the Frontend and the Backend, I work building interactive and user-friendly interfaces with full-power server-side services, including complex integrations with third-party tools.

#### Web Developer at Vaillant Media Web Solutions 02/2019 - 06/2021

Provided web solutions for clients both in Brazil and Portugal. Services would include web design and web development.

# **Projects**

### Bughash - 01/2021

Bug tracker app with support for description, image uploading, and time tracking.

Built with React, TypeScript, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, and Firebase Storage.

Link to the live project: **Bughash** 

### Coronalnfo App (Real time Map & Chart) - 01/2021

Covid-19 tracker with the latest data. Built with ReactJs using the <u>Disease.sh</u> API for external data

Link to the live project:  $\underline{\textit{CoronaInfoApp}}$ 

#### Ordenô Store - 2/2021 - 6/2021

Full stack MERN E-commerce application with cart and PayPal functionality built in React, React-Bootstrap, Redux, Sass, NodeJs, ExpressJs and MongoDB and Mongoose.

Link to the live project: Ordenostore

# Languages Spoken

- English (C2)
- Portuguese (Native Speaker)
- German (B2)
- Spanish (B1)

# Education / Certificates

Modern JavaScript From The Beginning - Udemy

ReactJs front to back - Udemy

Building full-stack apps with MongoDB, Express.js, React.js and Node.js - Udemy